(808) 649-0048

Beaverton, OR 97006

Email: equilinguin@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/elizabeth-garcia-guilinguin-207834191

GitHub: https://github.com/equilinguin

Elizabeth Garcia-Quilinquin

Full Stack Developer with experience in astronomy outreach to better build a web experience for the public in technology. Recently earned a certificate in Full Stack Developer at the University of Oregon, and prior knowledge of coding with the University of Hawaii Astronomy program. Some skills developed from the University of Oregon include: Javascript/jQuery, Web API, NodeJS, ES6. Known as a fast learner, I can pick up new skills and knowledge in an ever-fast-growing field like technology. My attention to detail helps with debugging code very quickly and precisely when combing through files. I've worked individually and in a group, to solve issues: I debug my code and pinpoint errors in my work and to help others debug project code. With my experience as a developer, I someday want to create new apps or computer applications that make a UI experience better education tools on the web.

APPLICATIONS

Burger App — https://stark-gorge-80987.herokuapp.com/

This app connects to a database and gives a user access to add to the database on an HTML page.

• HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Font Awesome, MySQL, Bootstrap

Weather Forecast — https://equilinguin.github.io/Weather-Forecast/

This app connects to a database and gives a user access to add to the database on an HTML page.

• HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, API

EXPERIENCE

Whole Foods Market, Hillsboro — Supervisor

May 2017 - PRESENT

- Oversee operations of department and supervise Team Members in their tasks
- Cook and prep for different food items that is displayed in our deli, hotbar, and prepack stations
- Write production lists for scheduled cooks in the kitchen

Oregon Museum of Science and Industry (OMSI), Portland — Space Science Educator

August 2017 - October 2019

- Present scheduled shows
- Educate guests on accurate information of astronomy
- Present full length star shows

Roxy's Island Grill, Beaverton — Manager

March 2014 - May 2017

- Training new employees on restaurant process and safety procedures
- FOH and BOH operations

• Filled orders for all restaurants

EDUCATION

University of Oregon, Portland, OR — Full Stack Web Development Certificate
October 2019 - April 2020

University of Hawaii, Hilo, HI — Bachelor's Degree in Science - Astronomy

August 2007 - December 2011